Editors.
So, yet another hour of questions,
so yeah,
please apologize if I will be like
sometimes a little bit slow in answering
to your question,
but it's actually good that I'm coming
from from the session from with your
competitors,
because I'll probably will be.
A little bit narrowing down the park,
because...
The feedback I had from the previous call
is, is it's too genetic, right?
And the little detail, blah blah blah,
so I'll try to be as much as specific as
possible,
but the same feedback we we gave.
to the guys from the previous session
that.
This is this is pretty much typical when
you you talk to C-level people,
they don't know.
many technical details.
And because on the call is just CEO,
there are no CTO or operational person,
the CEO not always can answer to all the
questions.
Yep.
Yeah, so, yeah, but at the same time,
I understand that you need to somehow
Exactly, yeah.
shape your solution.
Alright, so you need some details,
and I will be trying to do it, like,
will try to do my bus to get those those
details.
Okay, and as information,
we have a lot of people on the call
Um...
because I guess Anna and Tital were not
available.
So I forwarded the invitation to the
other squad.
So you can see we have got 17 people on
the call. So it's not just your squad,
Yeah.
right? So that's going to be, you know,
I thought, okay, they ask. So
Thank you for that.
Okay.
We try to coordinate before this call to
see if we can have some structure and
order, but we'll see how we, you know,
if we're able to run this.
Not everybody's going to ask questions,
I guess, but...
Okay, so the way how it would work,
you raise your hand,
and then based on the sequence,
you will be like unmuting yourself and
asking the question. Okay,
so let's move on. I'm Hugo.
Let's get started. And by the way,
I am not...
Like, very familiar,
familiar with the business itself and
business demand, right? So,
some question will be just my
interpretation, it's nothing with reality,
right?
But you have more information on the
scenario, no?
Or you just making things up?
Well, because there were questions like,
is it legal or not legal? I don't know.
Yeah, okay.
All right, so what I tried,
what I asked the team is to try to still
Okay, okay.
follow a structure,
like following the guidelines we had on
the questioning, you know,
from from broad funnel to narrow funnel,
so we can have a,
we don't go jump all over the place,
but we'll see if we if we manage to do
this. So,
And, and I think,
and I think we can go straight to the
Okay.
questions, right?
Rather than do a context, yeah, in time.
Uh, uh.
Yeah, see,
Krzysztof was going to do the context
Yeah, we kind of.
setting, but um, Krzysztof,
if you want to add a few things.
Yeah, probably.
I...
Okay, we can skip it. It's fine.
We already did it. Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Let's go to the questions.
Yeah, they.
The concept is pretty much simple, right?
So I'm CEO, I want to grow my business.
Mhm.
In order to grow my business,
I want to optimize operation team.
I want them to be as productive as most
of them because I don't want to grow
operation team.
I want to grow the business,
but I don't want to grow operation team.
Go ahead.
Alright.
Okay, so if I may start,
I'm not sure if I'm following the
sequence mentioned by Benoit,
but let's hope.
So my main question is that there was two
AI projects mentioned which were failed.
What was the reason they were failed?
I mean, specifically, what made them fail?
accuracy, trust, workflow fit, UX, money.
Ihar.
You mean the chatbot?
Yeah,
there was a chatbot and the
recommendation engine.
The chat was deployed to actually to
hospitals, and because we are,
because we are like operating on the
competitive market, right,
for the hospitals,
it was not the right solution, right?
Because chatting with us with our chat
bot and then chatting with chat bot from
other other other.
competitor was not the option.
And then the second one was they did my
recommendation.
Recommendation engine.
I think that it was making too many
mistakes.
But when I say to make too many mistakes,
We haven't done any like precise
investigation,
but it might be a combination of...
Technical.
Gaps in in the solution,
and 2nd not enough training which we put
towards the stuff.
OK, X.
I give the chance for others.
I have one question then.
So when a shift goes unfulfilled, is it,
what's the most common reason for the
shift to be unfulfilled?
Is it because there's just not enough
nurses around or because of other reasons?
Well, okay, so we do have their database.
of nurses. So they usually come to us,
they go through the onboarding process
where we share all the qualifications,
we do their profile.
So basically they go through that
onboarding process,
then this is a separate process.
From time to time,
we recheck that qualification. And again,
this is a separate team.
This is not my team,
which is like coordinator team,
which is machine request from the
hospitals to nourish it. Separate project.
Uh...
And again,
I mentioned that we are in the
competitive market.
Hospitals usually submit requests,
not just to us.
Meaning that if we don't supply,
then someone will supply.
So far,
it's not a big problem for me because...
The database of nurses we currently have,
it's enough,
but I want to grow the business.
We will be growing database of the nurses,
Okay.
and this is for my marketing team to
attract more businesses and attract more
Uh, nurses.
Okay.
So then the main reason why you're not
fulfilling some of the nurses is because
it takes too long to respond to the
hospital.
Yeah, because this is, yeah, exactly.
This is the competitive market, right?
So if someone submits quicker than I do,
then hospital can make decision quicker
and select someone else.
Ekaterina, go ahead.
Is it not?
Yeah.
Yeah,
I wanted to jump back to the previous
question regarding the failed AI projects
that you mentioned,
the chat bot that hospital staff rejected.
It was because they prefer the
conservative existing submission
channels like email, portal, and phone,
and which one you actually use more.
They still prefer to use emails.
Uh, but it's probably the biggest,
the biggest channel.
The.
As I mentioned,
the chat bot was only specific for us,
but we are not the only supplier for that.
That's one of the reasons.
Mhm.
OK, thank you, Rajesh.
Do you want to next question?
Yeah, so on a typical day,
where do your coordinators spend most of
their time? And if you, I mean,
if what's the part of the day that if you
could cut into half would make the
biggest difference to the business?
Well,
the best person to answer to your
question would be my head of operation,
but from the top of my head,
the usual day of...
A coordinator looks like they scan
request and then match potential
candidates who actually confirm their
availability to a specific slot request
Mhm.
by hospital.
That's matching availability of people,
their profile.
This is the biggest,
the biggest time-consuming part.
Great, thank you.
Uh, where's next, Josiane?
Hi, yeah,
so my question is around the 7% rate
mismatch.
Could you tell me exactly how do you
Yeah.
gather this statistic?
Because I would like to know what this
link goes.
It's purely based on the data we get from
the hospital. They say they...
Yeah.
The other rejected because of the...
That qualification mismatch to the to the
to the.
Ohh.
To the request, and 2nd is...
Again,
because we're in competitive market,
they sometimes select.
preferred candidates not only by their
qualification mesh,
but actually based on the feedback that
North have, specific North have.
Okay, thank you. So, yeah, basically,
it seems like the speed is one of the
But.
main issues here. Would you say that?
Pete and still qualification.
I still like machine requested the
qualification of the person.
So you just said on the mismatch part,
you said that the nurse don't always then
Okay, thank you.
What, what, what?
use the actual facts,
they just from their knowledge,
because her hospital liked her nurse or
maybe it was okay,
even though she doesn't have the
qualification or certification, you still,
Provide that nurse to the hospital.
Well, still,
the final decision is with hospital,
right? They decide with whom to go, right?
Our role is to submit the best matching
Mhm.
profile as possible. And yeah, I mean,
again, this is competitive market.
We better to offer something than nothing.
Yeah, OK, Tamas, go ahead, you went next.
Yeah, you've mentioned 2.
4 hours average time to fill,
but what the distribution?
Are there big deviations over there,
like 12 hours,
or this is rather going around 4 hours
and that's it, like maximum 30 minutes?
Yeah, it's around 4 hours here,
if you would think. Normally,
it's never goes beyond that,
because it's basically about mashing.
It's, it's, actually,
this is a question of Q,
because the team is limited, right?
Sometimes we get more required than usual,
and that's why...
Sometimes we handle requests longer than
usual.
So it's a combination of number of
incoming requests.
And capacity we have.
and what exactly the team need to do.
But there are no hours in delays or...
M.
Again,
it occasionally may happen that it takes
longer than four hours.
Sometimes it may take quicker just
because the queue is short.
And we have enough people to handle it
immediately. Like, if we see the request,
we can handle it immediately.
It's not like sitting in the queue for
some period of time.
Okay. Thanks.
Thanks. Before I move to the next month,
can I ask a question?
Can you walk us through the, you know,
on a given day when you get a request and
all the way to fulfillment?
Can you walk us through that process?
What are the nurse doing?
What data are they accessing?
How do they make the decision?
Could you go through the process?
Nor so operational person. Sorry,
could maybe I didn't get the question.
Question is to walk us through an actual
fulfillment of a nurse.
So from the time you had a request from
the hospital via different means to the
time you actually,
the hospital confirms that yes, indeed,
they want the nurse.
Could you walk us through that process?
End to end.
Again,
this question is probably to my head of
operations, but high level is again,
there is a queue,
someone pick ups the request,
try to find the machine person,
qualification plus availability on that
specific slot.
And the matching,
that matching is done through,
And then...
you use a database with everything you
need to know, credential, proximity,
availability, hospital preferences,
nurse preferences,
Yeah.
all that is actually stored in the
database.
That's everything sit there all together
separately, right? So profile of nurse,
it's separate.
availability of that specific person,
request from the hospital, again, slot,
they would like that person to attend,
and the qualification requirement.
So it's everything need to be matched.
Is this so?
Together,
that the biggest challenge might seem
like saying.
Currently,
are there any systems that manages this
I mean.
or is it all manual and is it in people
head?
Well, the Artem show shows capabilities,
but...
You know, it's people you really like.
making some search,
they pick up a request and then do some
search and then trying to match nurses.
Some people do have,
because they work in the company for a
long time,
they can do it quicker than others.
Like newcomers,
Yeah.
usually for newcomers take longer.
To find the right match.
So, the data is...
But we at the moment.
Sorry to interject.
So the data is in the spreadsheets or is
Yeah.
in, you know, well-organized databases,
that sort of thing.
It's a database.
Okay, thank you.
And on that note as well, the credentials,
for example,
when it comes in the emails or phone or
the portal,
is this structured data or is a free text
form?
So the hospitals can submit some sort of
blurb.
Wait, text.
Sorry?
Free text, free text.
Free text, okay,
but we do have some sort of
classification in the systems to which we
need to match this credentials in free
text to the structured credentials that
need to be verified later by compliance.
This is done by humans,
so they they go through request and they
do the matching.
Try to try to match it to the specific
categories that are set in the database.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
OK, thanks.
Natalia, go ahead.
Just A pull-up question on the integrated
system you might have.
So all the credentials are verified
before the nurse joined the roster,
but is MedFlex receiving push
notification from the system?
Is it as scheduled?
export or is someone manually checking
the portal?
Okay,
so there is actually a centralized system
around ServiceNow.
So all the requests go through,
even if they come through email or portal,
they still lend into the ServiceNow.
If.
And then my team is actually...
working directly with ServiceNode,
but it's still all the data is in a
pretty much raw format.
And so, if it's email,
it's just a free text;
they see only free text,
so ServiceNow is mostly used to manage
the queue.
OK, Karina.
Yeah, summarizing what you mentioned,
that compliance verification and matching
process basically run in parallel,
and you prioritize to propose at least
someone, then no one.
So it means that compliance is not such a
priority rather than availability.
If some nurse is not fully matching all
criteria and compliance,
would you still propose this person?
I don't think I mentioned they are
parallel processors.
I read that I mentioned they are
independent.
Meaning that it's process of nurses
onboarding is absolutely separate process.
Yeah.
While availability of nurses,
this is pretty much dynamic process,
right?
So because nurses might or might not be
But.
available on specific days or even hours,
This is up to them.
Just to be the availability.
So, as part of this compliance,
the licenses, certifications,
Stop.
and background checks,
when in the process does this happen?
As in when the noise joins the roster,
and then periodically it gets checked
Onboarding.
Yes, yeah.
when it gets expired,
and do you get any and you get any
Yeah, yeah.
notifications?
That's Compliance team.
I'm not currently to optimize it for this.
OKOK.
Thank you.
But are there any processes to keep these
databases like up to date? For example,
the...
Yeah, absolutely.
the availability,
who is updating availability of the
nurses and also who is.
Availability of nurses, I mentioned it,
availability of nurses is subject to
nurses to update themselves, right,
because only they know the availability.
Good.
All right. Qualification checks.
It's for my legal team.
Yes.
But do you have?
There is a cadence where they are legally
obligated to recheck qualification as a
separate process.
Periodically, OK.
Here you are declare, yeah,
regulated by law.
Is that done for an API or is it done for
an API or is that done manually,
the compliance verification?
The.
What, what, what is EPI?
Well,
do so there's a database of of the of the
compliance or the verification of the
nurses, yes, for their credentials.
Do we access that through?
I don't know. I mean,
I don't have any issues there, right?
So I don't think we need to talk too much
about that.
Okay.
So the compliance verification is not a,
not an issue.
Not an issue.
We don't think we need to actually focus
on that.
So.
And there is not an issue that it is kept
up to date and also the availability is
also assumed that is kept up to date by
the nurses themselves.
Correct.
And we have correct data to access for.
Okay.
Correct. Yeah.
I.
Alright, it's more to Chris,
you've been on the other question.
Yeah,
mine's a bit more high level actually.
So obviously you've got competitors in
the market and I'm guessing they've all
got the same access to the nurses as you
have.
Do you know what gives them potentially
the edge over submitting them quicker
than you? And if you both submit the same
nurse,
do you know what process is in place to
decide which agency they go with?
Yeah,
we do have like inside information that
some nurses are like in contract with
other.
agencies like we.
And we do have feeling that sometimes
they...
Well, as I mentioned before,
that's up to hospital to accept specific
person or not.
Ohh.
Sometimes nurses accepting other agencies
just because they pay a little bit more
than we are,
and sometimes it's the other way around.
Again,
because this is a competitive market,
so we are,
based on the contract we have with the
hospital,
We we can give that person specific
person, I mean, applying nurse.
Oh.
Be so bad.
Uh...
Right.
S.
Some competitors may have other contract
with the hospital,
and they might be in a position to give
higher ed for the nurse.
Or maybe they compromise with that margin.
We don't know.
But it's pretty much possible that the
same nurse will be submitted by two
different agencies. And then again, it's
Up to for people to decide to decide with
whom to proceed.
All right, Giuseppe, you next?
Okay, so my question is around hospitals.
Do all hospitals impose the same
constraint or are some, you know,
more easy to trust and others are more
picky and the requirements are consistent
with each other or the difference between
them?
All the there is some flexibilities.
The for some hospitals we are rather
Oops, stop, stop.
prefer it agency and it's.
Job of my sales team to be.
On that preferred list.
of supply agencies.
So it's more like in the commercial side
of thing rather than operational.
OK,
you don't have a particular statistics
about, you know,
what are the requirements if we had to
consider, you know,
all of the hospitals you are working with?
Yeah.
I think there might be some deviations,
but normally everyone operates on the
regulated market,
and so they often spenders.
OK, thank you.
Thanks.
Okay, then if there is a wrong match,
what is the cost of it? Is it reversible?
Yeah.
And if not,
then is it MetFlex or the hospital or the
nurse who suffers?
No, uh, well...
If, if it's not a match,
it's because they...
Hospitals, they made the final decision.
It's more in reputational area for us,
right? So...
Our job is to make the best,
to offer to them the best possible match.
All right, so,
so start the reputational and...
Okay.
To.
but no direct financial impact.
Okay,
and if in case an agent would say 70%
confident the nurse is a fit.
What would you do with that?
Match it anyway or escalate it or on hold
or what will be your decision?
Um...
Sometimes, it's on uh, um, calculators.
Uh, the children, so they decided,
would it make sense to submit or not?
So yeah,
it's more like there is no yet
well-defined.
But what was the practice or what's your
feeling? How would they act?
According.
Yeah, because again,
this is a competitive market and we are
not the only agency who will be
submitting candidates.
We would prefer submit.
at least something than nothing and let
the hospital decide and balancing that
reputational side of things which I
mentioned before.
Okay.
So it so it did not exact number 7050.
It sometimes is more on a on a on a.
I had the team experience working with
specific hospitals.
So would you require a coordinator to
validate a match?
So if an AI agent would propose a nurse
as a match,
would you require human in the loop?
So require a coordinator to actually say,
yes, okay, I agree,
let's propose it to the hospital or let
the agent just submit?
Um...
I'm not an expert in this area,
to be honest. I mean, if you say yes,
you don't need human in the loop.
SS.
Then I would rely on the Ardito.
Okay, from your answer,
you seem to say that you said that it's
okay if it doesn't know,
if it's not a complete match,
we'd rather submit someone a nurse than
nothing.
So it sounds like there is margin for
error,
do not concern about compliance or others.
Or am I misunderstood?
Did I misunderstand?
I'm just hoping this is not something you
do for the first time, so you know, like,
what are the consequences of removing
humans from the lobe? So yeah,
I'm all yours. Tell me.
Yeah, we do.
We do have some experience and we can put
some risk tolerance in the system, right,
to flag if we,
that's why I think Tamas was asking about
the 70%,
because we could also do something like
this where we would propose that if a
match doesn't seem completely like 90%
matching, we can then
ask a coordinator to review,
would that be something that would work
for you?
Yeah,
as soon as you give me the list of recent,
like potential consequences,
I'm happy to make the decision.
Okay.
Ekaterina, you are next.
You mentioned that you want to grow,
essentially,
set your goal is to grow the business 10
times more without needing to expanding
Okay.
personnel 10 times more, yeah? So,
and we know about the pain points,
Mm.
like the average time to for this process
takes for
for up to more of the four hours,
and that mismatch rate is 7%,
and no-share rate is 12. So,
maybe there are other pain points and
what that prevent you to grow the
business, so expand it too much, or which,
if it's only the three,
what will be the most painful?
Yeah.
I want to be flexible because this is
competitive marketing, and yes,
we do have plans to grow the business,
but I want to be flexible on.
On and actually be prepared as a business
to grow the number of people I have in
the separation team to support the
business, but it need to be.
very streamlined from onboarding
perspective. So I want to be flexible.
I don't want to spend too much time to
train the people. This is, by the way,
one of my biggest problem.
I need to train people.
So my operation team required quite
significant training so they could match
profiles and requests.
And I want it to be as simple as possible
for now.
Right,
including including onboarding time of
that new personnel,
if I would need to grow it.
So,
your pain point is rather the onboarding
of your own personnel,
since you still will expand the amount of
colleagues working on this, not...
It's not a pain for me at the moment
because my team is pretty much stable at
Mmh.
the moment.
But if I would grow my business,
maybe I would need to grow the...
Okay.
the personal team as well. I don't want,
but maybe I would need.
And I don't want to spend a lot for the
training.
If we apply the AI to your processes,
you probably would be able to get a lot
more shift matching with your aid
coordinators. Their work would change,
learning more to use the agents than
actually doing the matching themselves.
Would that, would that work?
Would your team be willing to transform
and change and start using AI?
Yeah, I just,
I just recalled it until a successful
machine engine, so let's see how it goes,
right?
Yes.
Yeah, no, no, Nazia.
Go next.
Natalia, sorry.
Yeah,
going back to compliance verification.
So if we imagine if a nurse credential
expires in, let's say, seven days,
and the shift is already being set for
two upcoming weeks, does the system know
beforehand that match is going to be
invalid or it's up to human.
Yes.
The system knows.
No, no, we we cannot.
We cannot offer a person,
we know that on their assignment date
that the certificate or the compliance is
invalidated and need to be rechecked.
Toots.
But that is manual, it's a manual check.
Right now.
Yeah, it is, but it's a regular one.
And sorry to follow up,
is that something that only surface when
the lapse actually happens?
Am I right?
Sorry, say it again, I'm not with you.
So,
the invalid shift is only will be
surfacing when the labs actually happens.
And in this case, you are manly.
But.
Verifying it.
But now, but coordinators again,
coordinators should not be.
Proposing nurses,
knowing that on the date of the...
Appointment.
A the the the the qualification
verification expired.
All right.
So it happens manually beforehand.
Yes,
all the qualification checks happens in
Mm.
advance on a regular schedule.
And I'd say indicated on the system that,
well, one day the expiration then is.
So if I just may jump in here,
it's a two-step process.
Thank you.
There's a parallel process for checking
the qualification,
the certification of the nurses,
separate process done regularly.
Yeah.
Mmh.
But then when a coordinator assigns or
finds a nurse,
he needs to verify in the system
that those certifications are valid.
It's straightaway available on the
specific NARS card.
Ohh.
Yeah, okay. Thanks. I guess so.
Let's go back to the... So, Rajiv,
Profile.
Ann.
your turn, I guess.
Yeah, yeah,
going back to the topic on nurses,
so you mentioned that the that is a,
I'm assuming when you say the nurses can
mark the availability,
it's a system and all and and you're
Mm.
happy with the system as of today and you
don't see.
Any problems with it?
Now, so far so good, we, well, the nurses,
the nurses need to have the flexibility
Thank you.
to mark where they're available,
where they're not. Yeah, so.
All right.
No problem there.
Giuseppe.
Sorry, you're the one next one.
Yeah, 2 questions.
You mentioned feedback for the nurses
from hospitals. Do you have access to it?
Access to where I center.
Access to feedback from hospitals.
Do you have access to it?
Maybe hospitals share with you this
feedback or something.
No,
we would ever get like a candidate
rejection, but it, and well,
when we bring new contract,
we usually talk to them and like try to
negotiate if we can do a better service,
but they...
Okay,
but what about different feedbacks from
different hospitals for the same nurse?
I mean,
we can match one nurse to one hospital,
you know, if the feedback was good.
Well, we...
We marked this in our systems, but...
Other agencies can do the same,
and the ranking system even might be kind
of different.
So,
I don't think there is like an industry
standard in this regard.
Okay, thank you. And another question,
does Nors have to accept or she only like
matches your availability and see?
They need to make their availability, uh,
and sometimes, uh, well, what happens,
they they...
They don't show up.
And we do have such cases.
So, we don't need to pre-acknowledge,
like we need to show,
Up.
like we accepted this assignment.
We do check no show up cases.
As soon as we see that this happening too
often with that specific person,
we actually can offboard the person from
our database.
Got to think.
So to just follow up on that, yeah,
I see there is a no-show rate of 12%.
So is that a big impact to your business?
Yes. Well,
it's difficult to say that big or small,
but obviously there is some impact and we
want to reduce that number as much as
possible. But as you can imagine,
it's not always in our power to do so.
But.
When we sometimes ask why you didn't show
up,
Well, people are not always honest, right?
So there might be so many different
reasons why.
including attending some other hospital
submitted by other agency,
but with Siarhei.
And when it happens,
does the MedFlex find out on its own
Right.
So.
before the shift or when the hospital
calls you?
Hospital call, unfortunately.
So.
So, we have, we have been notified, yeah,
we we are notified by the hospital that
someone didn't show up.
And how do you manage the nurses
requirements as in if the nurse says I
Mm.
want this,
I'm looking for this kind of job or you
know, the location preferences basically,
where is it maintained the nurses
preferences versus the hospital
preferences and the individual client
preferences?
I think the most important part is
qualification and second is actually
preferences, right?
So if you're not qualifying for the job,
Yeah.
but you prefer to have it,
legally it's not possible, right?
So you need to be qualified first and
then we
count on the preferences,
much in preferences of nurse and hospital.
Yeah, so is it managed manually,
or is that a system where you could?
It's all the way manual at the moment.
Okay.
So, to following up on that one,
so the process after our nurse is matched,
then compliance is checked,
and then if all good,
then someone calls the the nurse that won
the shift.
to confirm that their availability and
that they can go and they're interested
and so on.
Is there such a process as well to,
after all, is matched up,
then the nurses get called to confirm to
reduce this no-show, right?
Now,
we fully learned the submission of the
availability.
So,
but then the nurse is somehow notified
that she needs to go there.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yeah, yes, we,
we...
So there's a system that notifies
automatically the...
Automatically,
as when identified that well,
well first when that person is proposed
to your hospital,
and then when it's accepted by
hospitality,
not then notification to them.
Okay,
but no process to confirm this manually
Okay.
by the coordinator that the nurse said,
yes, I'm going.
Normally,
it's confirmed through the SMS or text
message. Sorry,
it's text message or email.
Oh.
And it's.
Sorry,
but you just mentioned that you don't
From whom to whom? From whom to whom?
The SMS.
capture.
No, nor should get notification from us.
via SMS that they got a shift somewhere.
Okay.
via SMS or email,
depending on their preferences.
Okay.
And the other question that I had is,
is there a specific part of the process
that you would not like to hand over
completely to an agent?
Is there a sensitive part or in this case,
in this industry,
there's no really real sensitivity here
that should be handled?
by someone in the process, specifically,
hand it over to a human to make this
decision.
Nothing I can recall.
Maybe there are some very specific
preferences.
Um, maybe, uh, sometimes we, we may have..
.
regular clients which require like almost
permanent nursery.
They may have their own preferences,
not very specific ones,
but because they'll...
Look.
So when the specific preferences come up,
someone needs to actually intervene in
the process and say yes or no.
Uhh...
We don't have any any indication that...
Specific requests need to be prioritized
over others.
All right,
so meaning that there might be some
specific requirements.
Which not that is a...
I can imagine that cannot be that easy to
be matched optimatically.
So you are okay with handing over a
process to an agent completely without
any...
Michael.
A specific decision in your business that
needs to be done by a person.
My goal,
my goal is automated as much as possible.
Yeah.
But are the but no sensitivities and no
something that in your business needs to
Are there any? Sorry, go.
Vegh.
be done by a human.
No, yeah, well...
Data protection is all the decision might
be in place, right?
But when you say sensitivity,
what do you mean specifically?
Any specific example?
that a decision to put a nurse into a
specific shift has a specific constraint
for a specific case that a human needs to
say, no,
we cannot put this nurse because it's too
risky or
something happens,
last time that we put it there was a
problem, so someone needs to be done that.
Or we just assign as long as they meet
the criteria, we assign them.
No one really needs to actually intervene
to check and say, yes, you did it okay,
agent, fine.
Unless,
unless there are no specific nodes in
nurse profile.
That's that shouldn't be an issue.
Okay.
Right, we have, we have.
Thanks.
For example, which nodes?
So, we have 15 minutes left in the call,
so I want to make sure that we also focus
on the top questions, but so Pavel,
go ahead and do the next next question.
Yeah,
for a small clarification regarding what
Alexander just asked,
you said that you notified the nurses
about these shifts they will have,
but do you receive any confirmation that
the nurse did this,
that they saw this confirmation that they
know that they have a shift?
By default, if not require,
meaning that they accept it. So they can,
for whatever reason, they can reply,
refusing it. It's possible. But actually,
they cannot reply. Actually,
they need to call us and say that
something changed in their schedule.
Okay, but if they basically miss this,
that means in your system,
you will count it as it accepted. In fact,
they don't know about the... Okay.
Yep, yep,
that that's up to them to to be like
available for for email notification and
being there.
network so they could see all the
incoming notification.
Okay.
And what are the time constraints between,
you know,
receiving identification and having the
physical shift? I mean,
like two or three days a week.
Um...
Yeah, because we, if they,
for whatever reason,
they they cannot show up and they they
must do notify us no longer than in 24
hours.
Okay, and you notify them in what advance?
Yeah,
usually it's happening two or three days
in advance.
Two, three days. Okay. And okay,
another more high level question. Yeah,
you know that you want to have everything
automated and we will try to do our best
to do that.
But maybe you have something specifically
that you would highlight as red flag for
automation.
Or I would say that you're kind of very
skeptical about automation.
Is there anything in your mind that you
can recall or not?
That.
You have a feeling that agent is very not
good enough for this work in your
Um...
personal feeling.
Mai.
The only the only thing I'm skeptical is
how accurate that matching process will
be,
and then the second one is how my people
will accept that agency flow because they
refused the previous solution.
I'm not sure how bad the solution was,
but I do have a feeling that it was like..
.
Lack of.
lack of training and lack of trust and
and actually partially
Thinking they're thinking that it might
be risk for their job security.
Okay, and the last one,
can I call that from what I see that the
matching process is the process where we
see the most, you know, absence of this,
not the absence,
presence of this gut feeling. I mean,
when the when the something is decided
not upon the instructions,
but rather than people have some,
you know, pattern in their head,
like this nurse would fit better,
this nurse would fit less without.
Any direct hints on that, you know,
based on the experience?
Yeah,
I do have for what very experienced
people in my team, someone,
some some people work for me,
like 10 more, 10 plus, yeah,
they're they actually do have.
As you mentioned, feeling.
Yeah.
Uh...
The.
They know how to act better in specific
cases,
assuming the specific request and even
sometimes specification of the
specialization of the hospital,
matching into the nurses.
Okay, thanks.
So, yeah, it's...
So let's say in a worst case...
Um, two months are still making.
In a worst case,
you will have eight different judgment
Yeah.
calls.
For the matching process.
Why?
if coordinators work on undocumented
rules.
There will be 8 different.
Mm.
judgment.
judgments in magic.
I'm not sure I'm following you.
I think Anatolii means that you have 8
workers, right?
And that the actual judgment upon that,
like, is this person fit,
Yes.
or let's say what the best person for
this specific schedule,
it can be 8 different, you know,
decisions from eight different people.
Okay, gotcha. Actually,
at the end of the day,
Yes.
I'm more about hospital satisfaction on
the specific person.
As soon as the hospital is happy,
I'm happy.
Thank you.
All right, Krzysztof.
Yes,
I've got a general question regarding a
cost of the no-show or the lost shift.
What are the consequences in terms of the
money or maybe it costed you some
relationship with the hospitals?
Did you ever lost the relationship with
the hospital?
Have I done answered this question
already?
Okay, so I need to.
I think you, yeah,
you mentioned that the reason there's an
offshore and it's more of the reason is
because the nurses get assigned by
another,
they go to another hospital because they
Yeah, yeah, but that's obvious.
But my actual question is,
have a...
can you estimate in terms of the actual
money? Like, do you have any range?
No,
it's more in a in a like relationship
with with my clients, yeah.
relationship.
But did you ever lose the relationship
with the hospital or it was rather the
degradation of the relationship but not
Nah.
losing it?
Not,
but I had to give a discount to one of my
clients.
So, somehow,
you might measure it in terms of the
financial loss.
Yeah, but it's not like black and white.
So, okay,
so no estimations were well done. Okay,
thank you.
Is this issues of no shore rate something
that you think should be addressed here
in with AI, if we can?
Are we actually solving solving that
changes all that? No show up problem here.
If we could, I would be more than happy.
Okay.
Well,
I would say it's somehow related because
it's about the speed.
So if you can increase the speed,
then we can solve or free the no-show
issue or the other ones or the better
matching or the quality and so on.
So definitely it's related.
Cool, then the more problems we solve,
the better.
That's.
Okay.
Yeah,
we have to drill into this one separately,
the no shore rate, it seems.
If I can ask a question before I let the
others, you mentioned,
I'm trying to understand the success
criteria,
you mentioned 10 times the business.
What would be a success metrics for you?
10 times,
we don't have the size of your business,
so would it be 10 times the number of
shift making? So, you know,
you do 120 a day today.
If we went up to 1200,
that would be a success metric.
So what would be a success metric?
Yeah,
more my target in a in a in the Q2 years
time to have 200 millions in revenue,
which in the current way is like 14.
What's the current? Sorry,
I couldn't hear it.
Okay.
The current revenue.
Fourteen.
Fourteen million millions want to go to
wants to go to 200 in two years.
14, okay.
Okay.
But it mentions that you'd like to do it
in eight weeks.
So in some of the information we got,
what would you expect to have in eight
weeks?
What I want in my ethics to grow my
business to 200.
In Edwards.
Touch.
No, well, it's a fair question,
but I want to actually to give the best
proposal what I can get into in those
eight weeks, right? So it...
I want to start addressing my progresses
as soon as possible.
So I want to get that away from my
investment as soon as possible.
So you tell me what is the best to do in
eight weeks so I could get my money back.
Starting to get my money back.
K.
One quick question.
What are the tasks for the senior
coordinator which is not visible by the
system?
Make sure that we are filling all the
requests as quick as possible,
and we there is no waiting queue.
Like if I see that there is a queue,
then it's actually a problem.
So my job is to make sure there is no
queue, because as I mentioned,
if there is a queue, then we actually,
it takes us even longer to submit our
proposal and time is a problem.
OK.
When you say there is no queue,
you mean like your 8 coordinators have
Yeah.
actually are working on all the tickets?
It's actually mean as we process all the
requests on the go.
Yeah.
Yep.
Tetiana.
In case if the same nurses are matching
to different hospital requests, do you,
how do you do personal reserves them?
So is it only one nurse that is
pre-reserved till the nurse will confirm
final?
availability or it's like reservation is
to three nurses for each request and
others hospital requests,
they are not visible for them.
It's not feasible for nurses at all.
We just submitted to hospital and then
notify them which hospital they need to
have to go. They have to go.
Ohh...
I mean, for you, not for nurses visible.
I mean, your coordinators, for example,
have three,
the same nurses that are matching to
different hospitals.
And do you reserve for each hospital one
nurse, which is matching or several?
No, it will not be no,
it will not be efficient for the business.
Mm.
Because other competitors do pretty much
the same.
Right,
so we submit a couple of nurses to
different hospitals,
and then as soon as someone is confirmed.
Mhm.
then we remove it from other hospital
submission.
OK, so at the same time,
you sent all three nurses to the same
different hospitals. OK,
and what if they all of them confirm the
Yeah, yep.
same nurse?
Then, then we work our proposal.
Okay.
We have two minutes left in our call.
Yeah.
Now, we we need actually need to finish,
and so let's stop the questions.
I'm back to my role of the coach, yeah.
Okay.
Any questions, guys?
about the session,
I do have one feedback which I actually
mentioned to other team as well.
I think you.
I don't know what the reason is, but...
You and the other team,
you focused a lot on that legal sort of
things. Like I, from the very beginning,
I mentioned that's a separate process.
There is a separate team on boarding the
nurses and for coordinators is available
if the nurse is like accepted properly on
boarded and can be offered you to the
hospital.
End of the story,
but you all for some reason been keep
asking this question. I'm not sure why.
I think that's, you know,
that's our training in a way.
We've been trained to look at risk and
compliance,
especially with AI and in that.
No, but as soon as I said,
that's separate thing,
Yeah.
nothing to do with the currency. Done.
What?
Can I ask just one more last question?
In terms of the coordinators,
what do you expect the impact to be from
this agentic implementation?
Because if we are able to automate
everything,
then what would be the job of the
coordinators? Are you expecting?
that layoffs will be also part of the
process.
Ohh.
You're worse than me to go back to my
role on CEO.
Sorry.
Yeah, it's gonna work. We don't,
do we do you need the answer? Alexandra,
Did we answer that? Because I mean,
are you really,
do you know, because...
It doesn't matter.
what happens to the coordinators?
If you are able to automate everything.
I mentioned that,
I mentioned that I want to grow my
business. So I would,
I'm expecting to more requests from the
hospitals with the same number of people
in my team.
But if we can automate the whole process,
yeah, exactly, exactly,
Or less people with the same amount of
hospital.
because you're expecting to automate
everything,
Okay. Okay.
then the coordinators will have less to
do, but,
and you don't want them to be in the loop
because you don't want any decisions for
On.
Up.
them to be made,
then what kind of work would they be
Doesn't matter.
doing?
We'll be happy to review a solution.
Yeah.
Sorry,
can I ask a question for you to as a
Okay.
coach, actually, if you don't mind?
I haven't asked you this as when you were
Yeah.
in the role, but what do you think?
When we talk to the CEOs,
should we actually understand their
strategic approach? I mean, for example,
AI transformation, right?
We can do it sharp, rapidly,
with a higher risk,
or we can do it in a conservatively.
with a more feedback loop and going
gracefully, step by step.
Is it something that we should actually
ask or is it something that we should
actually push them to do?
What is the better approach?
It's a very good question,
but depending on the size of the
organization,
maturity of the organization,
some CEO just heard that there is some
something like AI,
but they have no idea how that AI can
help to their business.
Some CEO are more advanced and they
clearly
Yeah.
themselves understand where AI could be
applicable to that business.
So unfortunately,
by all I think there is no single recipe,
right? You just need to feel that person,
like is a person actually
Yeah, but I mean as EPAM we...
Yeah.
has already some ideas, right?
What is his current knowledge of AI or is
just articles saying that AI can change
your business and period, right?
Nothing more than that.
Like reality and marketing, noise,
two different things.
Right.
Okay, I'll rephrase.
And I think our, and I think our, our...
Like,
goal at the at the at the partner of
decline is actually to educate them and
say, "That's that's doable,
that's not yet doable."
That would work, that wouldn't.
I've.
But this, but as a long-term goals,
I mean, for us, for the EPAM,
let's say we should make them more like
make our clients happy or make our
clients' business efficient,
even if it can meet, you know,
some resilience at the beginning,
what what we do prioritizing,
or also depends, I mean,
that's also the answer.
Yeah.
I think it's been told by the C-level a
long, long time ago,
if our clients are successful with their
business, then we are good as well.
If they are not successful in their
business,
then at some point we just do not have
that client.
Okay.
Going back to the...
So, sometimes we need to push them.
But it.
Going back to the scenario,
because you know we still want to,
But I think it.
the reason also that I think people ask
about the compliance, the verification,
it's because the, you know,
when we run our AI on discovery,
one of the top work stream that could be
agentic is the verification.
Like, I, I run the, you know,
we run the thing that were the two work
streams that that come up is the matching
and the second one is verifying the
compliance,
and that's why I think you know,
we because we said, "Ohh no, I don't,
I don't need it, I don't need it,
Okay.
that's why maybe I,
at least that's why I kept asking, so,
but not even kept asking, but you know,
ask one or two questions and people maybe
also ask for that."
That's one of the reason, I think.
Okay, look, I think if this is the case,
then we are expecting for you from you
too much, right?
So I would prefer you at least solve one
business problem, but solve it properly,
because they're two different problems.
Right, one is that the verification,
and 2nd is the operation of the of the
coordinators, right?
Yeah,
but you know how sometimes the CEO may
think the problem is somewhere and when
you start digging, actually, you know,
you can save them also increase the
business because you solved the other
problem that they didn't mention,
what they thought wasn't a problem.
So that's why, you know, I don't know,
we don't know how much trick you put in
the scenario yet.
No, no, look, you're actually right.
If I will be growing my business,
It's a...
then that verification process will...
Yeah.
Increases well, alright, in demand.
Maybe then I will have to put something
Exactly.
there as well, but...
Two different facts,
still two different paths,
like two different teams.
It's not the same single process.
Yeah.
And what I find, I guess,
in this session with the customer here is
to follow the script of understanding,
you know, what the cognitive load,
where is the breakpoints. We didn't quite,
I don't know that we addressed it in this
call to then get to the point where, okay,
what works.
So it sounds from what you said, see,
the work stream we need to focus on is
the intake or the
Actually, the matching, right?
That's what when we should the business
problem we need to focus,
and then after that,
but to understand after that what job to
be done inside that work stream can be
agentic, not sure we got, you know, the...
to get that answer in this call, but...
Yeah.
By the way, the.
classification, come on,
qualification check.
It might not be even fully written on my
team as such, right? So,
because it's pretty much formal process.
It's the same like validating if someone
submitted a license.
How can I check that this is actually a
valid license?
I will use such party service, right? Say.
..
Yeah, I mean, we we can pop this,
even even if we focus on this just one
And.
matching part, you know,
just to feedback on the on the call,
like how we run the call and whether we
were able to understand the cognitive
load and what we can delegate and and and
you know, with all the breakpoints,
I'm not sure we actually had all the.
Questions for that yet, but...
Yeah.
Yes.
And yeah, I apologize, guys. First of all,
I need to go on a second. Yeah,
don't get all the, like,
my responses as a source of like complete
truth,
which is actually may happen on the
market. That's again,
I was like trying to find the answer that
Yeah.
sometimes in the goal and sometimes
Uh, when I had a call with a reply,
it sounds like a rubbish.
All right.
Alright, anyone? I guess we we overtime,
so anyone wants to ask,
add anything or ask anything else?
I don't think we catch any contradictions,
did we?
Yeah.
I think we did.
I want to logical.
Ohh, OK.
The main contradiction.
For example...
When I assume that, uh-huh, yes.
No, I think.
I think was was one actually I was just
thinking how it actually could work if we
submit nurses to multiple like hospitals.
Alright, is the...
I don't know. I don't know, really.
I mean.
Yeah, just work with what I told, right?
But it's might not be the other thing,
Yeah,
but that happens with the competitor,
right? That same note.
might not be the other thing.
Yeah,
and the same nurse may also be assigned
by another vendor as well, right?
While you were trying to assign her or
we've already assigned and she gets
assigned somewhere, it's got to be,
that's why they know the no-show and then,
yeah, it's going to be quite difficult to.
To get to the point we actually, yeah.
Yeah.
Second currency question.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
More of a design, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay, good luck, guys.
Thanks, Alexandra. That was fun.
Alright, thanks a lot. It was fun.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Bye.
Thank you. Bye. Thank you.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
Bye.
Adeel.
I.